saiyaman.info 2016-12-05

# Privacy Policy | Anime Malay dot NET

## Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Animemalay.net** is committed to protecting your privacy,  **Animemalay.net** values the privacy of our members and users.  **Animemalay.net** does not sell, trade, share or rent your personal information to other companies. This includes your e-mail address, name, and location. Upon surfing to  **Animemalay.net** such things as your IP address, hostname, location, browser application are logged for statistical and security reasons. The statistical are handle by  **Animemalay.net** itself and third-parties “Google Analytics”.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a very small text file placed on your system upon logging on to  **Animemalay.net** (and most other websites). This file serves as your identification card and is uniquely yours, and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Children’s Privacy**  
**Animemalay.net**  does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 13. We make reasonable efforts to prevent someone who is underage from joining as a member of **Animemalay.net** , and will not collect information from them.

**Third Parties**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Third Party websites may collect information from users (anonymous include) of **Animemalay.net** , this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that.
